<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>🔨 Timothy Track</title>
      <link>https://bosgid.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on 🔨 Timothy Track</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>1 - Introduction to Systematic Theology</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/1---Introduction-to-Systematic-Theology</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/1---Introduction-to-Systematic-Theology</guid>
    <description>Define systematic theology and discuss its relationship with other theological disciplines (historical theology, philosophical theology, apologetics, Old Testament theology, New Testament theology, and biblical theology).</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:34:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>10 - Angels, Satan, and Demons</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/10---Angels,-Satan,-and-Demons</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/10---Angels,-Satan,-and-Demons</guid>
    <description>What are angels? § Angels Angels are created spiritual beings with moral judgment and high intelligence but without physical bodies. Angels have not always existed; they are part of the universe that God created (Neh 9:6; cf.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:47:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>11 - The Creation of Man</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/11---The-Creation-of-Man</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/11---The-Creation-of-Man</guid>
    <description>What was the purpose for which God created man? On that basis, what is to be the primary purpose of our lives? § As we have seen in Chapter 4, God does not need anything and there is nothing that He lacks.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:39:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>12 - Man as Male and Female</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/12---Man-as-Male-and-Female</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/12---Man-as-Male-and-Female</guid>
    <description> Note Genesis 5:1-2 This is the book of the generations of Adam. When God created man, he made him in the likeness of God. Male and female he created them, and he blessed them and named them Man when they were created.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:12:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>13 - Sin</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/13---Sin</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/13---Sin</guid>
    <description>Define sin. § Sin Sin is any failure to conform to the moral law of God in act, attitude, or nature. Acts that go against the moral law of God are easy to identify: stealing, lying, murder, adultery, etc.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:22:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>14 - The Person of Christ</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/14---The-Person-of-Christ</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/14---The-Person-of-Christ</guid>
    <description>Give three evidences from Scripture for the humanity of Christ. § The Virgin Birth The birth of Jesus by a human mother is well recorded in the Gospels (Matt 1:18-25; Luke 1:26-35, Luke 2:6-7).</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>15 - The Atonement</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/15---The-Atonement</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/15---The-Atonement</guid>
    <description> The Atonement The atonement is the work Christ did in his life and death to earn our salvation. To which two aspects of God’s character can we trace the ultimate cause of the atonement? § The ultimate cause of the atonement was God’s love and justice.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:41:15 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>16 - Resurrection and Ascension</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/16---Resurrection-and-Ascension</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/16---Resurrection-and-Ascension</guid>
    <description>Did Jesus have a physical body after his resurrection? Give scriptural support for your answer. § There are at least ten pieces of evidence in the New Testament showing that Jesus had a physical body after the resurrection: The disciples “took hold of his feet” (Matt 28:9); he appeared to the disciples on the road to Emmaus to be just another traveller on the road (Luke 24:15-18, 28-29); he took bread and broke it (Luke 24:30); he ate a piece of broiled fish (Luke 24:43) to demonstrate clearly that he had a physical body and was not just a spirit; Mary thought him to be a gardener (John 20:15); “he showed them his hands and his side” (John 20:20); he invited Thomas to put his finger out to touch his hands and put out his hand and touch his side (John 20:27); he prepared breakfast for his disciples (John 21:12-13); and he explicitly told them, “See my hands and my feet, that it is I myself.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 19:10:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>17 - Common Grace</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/17---Common-Grace</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/17---Common-Grace</guid>
    <description> Common Grace Common grace is the grace of God by which he gives people innumerable blessings that are not part of salvation. If the punishment for sin is death (Rom 6:23), how can God continue to give blessings to mankind? § God, in His mercy, has chosen to continue to bestow blessings onto mankind even though through sin we deserve death.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 08:29:15 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>18 - Election</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/18---Election</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/18---Election</guid>
    <description>Define election, and give three evidences from the New Testament in support of this doctrine. § Election Election is an act of God before creation in which he chooses some people to be saved, not on account of any foreseen merit in them, but only because of his sovereign good pleasure.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 18:41:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>