<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>๐จ Timothy Track</title>
      <link>https://bosgid.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on ๐จ Timothy Track</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Bible Doctrine (Second Edition)</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)</guid>
    <description> Info ยง Author: Wayne Grudem Publication Date: 05 April 2022 Pages: 672 Tags:#faith,#faith/doctrine 1 - Introduction to Systematic Theology ยง Define systematic theology and discuss its relationship with other theological disciplines (historical theology, philosophical theology, apologetics, Old Testament theology, New Testament theology, and biblical theology).</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>01 - Genesis</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/01---Genesis</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/01---Genesis</guid>
    <description> Genesis 1 ยง Genesis 2 ยง Genesis 3 ยง Genesis 4 ยง Genesis 5 ยง Genesis 6 ยง Genesis 7 ยง Genesis 8 ยง Genesis 9 ยง Genesis 10 ยง Genesis 11 ยง Genesis 12 ยง Genesis 13 ยง Genesis 14 ยง Genesis 15 ยง Genesis 16 ยง Genesis 17 ยง Genesis 18 ยง Genesis 19 ยง Genesis 20 ยง Genesis 21 ยง Genesis 22 ยง Genesis 23 ยง Genesis 24 ยง Genesis 25 ยง Genesis 26 ยง Genesis 27 ยง Genesis 28 ยง Genesis 29 ยง Genesis 30 ยง Genesis 31 ยง Genesis 32 ยง Genesis 33 ยง Genesis 34 ยง Genesis 35 ยง Genesis 36 ยง Genesis 37 ยง Genesis 38 ยง Genesis 39 ยง Genesis 40 ยง Genesis 41 ยง Genesis 42 ยง Genesis 43 ยง Genesis 44 ยง Genesis 45 ยง Genesis 46 ยง Genesis 47 ยง Genesis 48 ยง Genesis 49 ยง Genesis 50 ยง .</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 1</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-1</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-1</guid>
    <description>Genesis 1 ยง 1 ยง In the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth. 2 ยง The earth was without form and void, and darkness was over the face of the deep.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 10</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-10</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-10</guid>
    <description>Genesis 10 ยง 1 ยง These are the generations of the sons of Noah, Shem, Ham, and Japheth. Sons were born to them after the flood. 2 ยง The sons of Japheth: Gomer, Magog, Madai, Javan, Tubal, Meshech, and Tiras.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 11</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-11</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-11</guid>
    <description>Genesis 11 ยง 1 ยง Now the whole earth had one language and the same words. 2 ยง And as people migrated from the east, they found a plain in the land of Shinar and settled there.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 12</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-12</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-12</guid>
    <description>Genesis 12 ยง 1 ยง Now the LORD said to Abram, โGo from your country and your kindred and your fatherโs house to the land that I will show you. 2 ยง And I will make of you a great nation, and I will bless you and make your name great, so that you will be a blessing.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 13</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-13</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-13</guid>
    <description>Genesis 13 ยง 1 ยง So Abram went up from Egypt, he and his wife and all that he had, and Lot with him, into the Negeb. 2 ยง Now Abram was very rich in livestock, in silver, and in gold.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 14</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-14</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-14</guid>
    <description>Genesis 14 ยง 1 ยง In the days of Amraphel king of Shinar, Arioch king of Ellasar, Chedorlaomer king of Elam, and Tidal king of Goiim, 2 ยง these kings made war with Bera king of Sodom, Birsha king of Gomorrah, Shinab king of Admah, Shemeber king of Zeboiim, and the king of Bela (that is, Zoar).</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 15</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-15</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-15</guid>
    <description>Genesis 15 ยง 1 ยง After these things the word of the LORD came to Abram in a vision: โFear not, Abram, I am your shield; your reward shall be very great.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Gen 16</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-16</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/Gen-16</guid>
    <description>Genesis 16 ยง 1 ยง Now Sarai, Abramโs wife, had borne him no children. She had a female Egyptian servant whose name was Hagar. 2 ยง And Sarai said to Abram, โBehold now, the LORD has prevented me from bearing children.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>