<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>๐จ Timothy Track</title>
      <link>https://bosgid.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on ๐จ Timothy Track</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>1 - Introduction to Systematic Theology</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/1---Introduction-to-Systematic-Theology</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/1---Introduction-to-Systematic-Theology</guid>
    <description>Define systematic theology and discuss its relationship with other theological disciplines (historical theology, philosophical theology, apologetics, Old Testament theology, New Testament theology, and biblical theology).</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>2 - The Authority and Inerrancy of the Bible</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/2---The-Authority-and-Inerrancy-of-the-Bible</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/2---The-Authority-and-Inerrancy-of-the-Bible</guid>
    <description>Defend the following statement: โAll the words in Scripture are Godโs words.โ ยง This is what the Bible claims for itself. OLD TESTAMENT In the Old Testament, the phrase โThus says the LORD,โ appears hundreds of times and was recognized as identical in form to the phrase, โThus says the Kingโ, which was used to preface the edict of a king to his subjects, an edict that could not be challenged or questioned, but that simply had to be obeyed.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>3 - The Clarity, Necessity, and Sufficiency of the Bible</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/3---The-Clarity,-Necessity,-and-Sufficiency-of-the-Bible</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/3---The-Clarity,-Necessity,-and-Sufficiency-of-the-Bible</guid>
    <description> Clarity of Scripture The clarity of Scripture means that the Bible is written in such a way that it is able to be understood, but right understanding requires time, effort, the use of ordinary means, a willingness to obey, and the help of the Holy Spirit; and our understanding will remain imperfect in this lifetime.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>4 - The Character of God โIncommunicableโ Attributes</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/4---The-Character-of-God-%E2%80%9CIncommunicable%E2%80%9D-Attributes</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/4---The-Character-of-God-%E2%80%9CIncommunicable%E2%80%9D-Attributes</guid>
    <description> Incommunicable Not able to be communicated to others/incapable of being communicated In addition to the Bible, what evidence do we have that God exists? ยง Two main ways: All people have an inner sense of God and evidence of God can be found in nature.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>5 - The โCommunicableโ Attributes of God</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/5---The-%E2%80%9CCommunicable%E2%80%9D-Attributes-of-God</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/5---The-%E2%80%9CCommunicable%E2%80%9D-Attributes-of-God</guid>
    <description>Name and differentiate between the two attributes that describe Godโs being. ยง Godโs Spirituality Godโs spirituality means that God exists as a being that is not made of any matter, has no parts or dimensions, is unable to be perceived by our bodily senses, and is more excellent than any other kind of existence.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>6 - The Trinity</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/6---The-Trinity</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/6---The-Trinity</guid>
    <description>Provide scriptural evidence for the doctrine of the Trinity from both the Old and New Testaments. ยง OLD TESTAMENT In Genesis 1:26, God said, โLet us make man in our Image, after our likeness.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>7 - Creation</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/7---Creation</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/7---Creation</guid>
    <description>Define the doctrine of creation. ยง Doctrine of Creation God created the entire universe out of nothing; it was originally very good; and he created it to glorify himself.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:44:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>8 - Godโs Providence</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/8---God%E2%80%99s-Providence</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/8---God%E2%80%99s-Providence</guid>
    <description> Godโs Providence God is continually involved with all created things in such a way that he keeps them existing and maintaining the properties with which he created them; cooperates with created things in every action, directing their distinctive properties to cause them to act as they do; and directs them to fulfill his purposes.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:44:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bible Doctrine (Second Edition)</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem/Bible-Doctrine-(Second-Edition)---Wayne-Grudem</guid>
    <description> Info ยง Author: Wayne Grudem Publication Date: 05 April 2022 Pages: 672 Tags: #faith,#faith/doctrine Chapter 1: Introduction to Systematic Theology ยง PART 1: The Doctrine of the Word of God ยง Chapter 2: The Authority and Inerrancy of the Bible ยง Chapter 3: The Clarity, Necessity, and Sufficiency of the Bible ยง PART 2: The Doctrine of God ยง Chapter 4: The Character of God โIncommunicableโ Attributes ยง Chapter 5: The โCommunicableโ Attributes of God ยง Chapter 6: The Trinity ยง Chapter 7: Creation ยง Chapter 8: Godโs Providence ยง.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>01 - Genesis</title>
    <link>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/01---Genesis</link>
    <guid>https://bosgid.github.io/The-Bible-(ESV)/01---Genesis/01---Genesis</guid>
    <description> Genesis 1 ยง Genesis 2 ยง Genesis 3 ยง Genesis 4 ยง Genesis 5 ยง Genesis 6 ยง Genesis 7 ยง Genesis 8 ยง Genesis 9 ยง Genesis 10 ยง Genesis 11 ยง Genesis 12 ยง Genesis 13 ยง Genesis 14 ยง Genesis 15 ยง Genesis 16 ยง Genesis 17 ยง Genesis 18 ยง Genesis 19 ยง Genesis 20 ยง Genesis 21 ยง Genesis 22 ยง Genesis 23 ยง Genesis 24 ยง Genesis 25 ยง Genesis 26 ยง Genesis 27 ยง Genesis 28 ยง Genesis 29 ยง Genesis 30 ยง Genesis 31 ยง Genesis 32 ยง Genesis 33 ยง Genesis 34 ยง Genesis 35 ยง Genesis 36 ยง Genesis 37 ยง Genesis 38 ยง Genesis 39 ยง Genesis 40 ยง Genesis 41 ยง Genesis 42 ยง Genesis 43 ยง Genesis 44 ยง Genesis 45 ยง Genesis 46 ยง Genesis 47 ยง Genesis 48 ยง Genesis 49 ยง Genesis 50 ยง .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>